WENXUAN WANG

 $\frac{wxwang.iris@gmail.com \mid wenxuan.wang@intel.com}{Homepage \mid Google Scholar}$

SUMMARY

I am currently a senior researcher in Intel Asia-Pacific Research Development Ltd. Before that, I have completed my PHD study at school of computer science in Fudan University, under the supervision of Prof. Xiangyang Xue. At present, I devote to the research of adversarial attacks, face recognition, generative adversarial networks, expression classification, person re-identification with deep learning. I have already published 9 academic papers, including 5 CCF-A papers (all as the first author), 1 CCF-B papers, 1 CCF-C papers and 1 chinese journal. I also have applied for 5 patents, 4 of them have been authorized.

EDUCATION

PHD of Science | *Computer Application* Fudan University

Sep. 2017 – Now Shanghai

Bachelor of Engineering | *Computer Science and Technology* Northwestern Polytechnical University

Sep. 2013 – Jul. 2017 Shaanxi

PUBLICATIONS

Conference

- DST: Dynamic Substitute Training for Data-free Black-box Attack. IEEE/CVF Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2022.
 Wanguan Wang, Yuglin Oian, Yanguai Fu, Yianggang Yug.
 - Wenxuan Wang, Xuelin Qian, Yanwei Fu, Xiangyang Xue.
- Delving into Data: Effectively Substitute Training for Black-box Attack. IEEE/CVF Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2021.

 Wanguan Wang Bangija Vin Taining Van Li Zhang Vanyaji Eu Shaubang Ding Jilin Li Feiyua
 - **Wenxuan Wang**, Bangjie Yin, Taiping Yao, Li Zhang, Yanwei Fu, Shouhong Ding, Jilin Li, Feiyue Huang, Xiangyang Xue.
- Adv-Makeup: A New Imperceptible and Transferable Attack on Face Recognition. International Joint Conference on Artificial Intelligence (IJCAI), 2021.
 Bangjie Yin*, Wenxuan Wang*, Taiping Yao*, Junfeng Guo, Zelun Kong, Shouhong Ding, Jilin Li, Cong Liu (* indicates equal contributions).
- FMMu-Net: Face Morphological Multi-branch Network for Makeup-invariant Face Verification. IEEE/CVF Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2020. Wenxuan Wang, Yanwei Fu, Xuelin Qian, Qi Tian, Yu-Gang Jiang, Xiangyang Xue.
- Long-Term Cloth-Changing Person Re-identification. Asian Conference on Computer Vision (ACCV), 2020. (Oral)
 - Xuelin Qian, **Wenxuan Wang**, Li Zhang, Fangrui Zhu, Yanwei Fu, Tao Xiang, Yu-Gang Jiang, Xiangyang Xue.
- Comp-GAN: Compositional Generative Adversarial Network in Synthesizing and Recognizing Facial Expression. ACM International Conference on Multimedia. (ACM MM), 2019.
 Wenxuan Wang, Qiang Sun, Yanwei Fu, Tao Chen, Chenjie Cao, Ziqi Zheng, Guoqiang Xu, Han Qiu, Yu-Gang Jiang, Xiangyang Xue.
- Pose-Normalized Image Generation for Person Re-identification. European Conference on Computer Vision. (ECCV), 2018.
 - Xuelin Qian, Yanwei Fu, Tao Xiang, Wenxuan Wang, Jie Qiu, Yang Wu, Yu-Gang Jiang, Xiangyang Xue.

• A COVID-19 Screening Method Based on Eyes Photographs and Artificial Intelligence. European Journal of Public Health, 2021.

Feng Li, Xiangyang Xue, Paula Boned Fustel, Shisong Rong, Qiang Sun, Haicheng Tang, **Wenxuan Wang**, Yanwei Fu, Ana Boned-Ombuena8, Mengwei Gu.

Journal

• IIRC-GAN: Towards Identity Inter-Relationship Consistent Face De-identification. Journal of East China Normal University (Natural Science), 2022.

Yifan Bu, Xiaoling Wang, keke He, Jianxing Lu, Wenxuan Wang(Corresponding Author).

Preprint

- A New Screening Method for COVID-19 based on Ocular Feature Recognition by Machine Learning Tools.
 - Yanwei Fu, Feng Li, **Wenxuan Wang**, Haicheng Tang, Xuelin Qian, Mengwei Gu, Xiangyang Xue. medRxiv, 2020.
- Learning to Augment Expressions for Few-shot Fine-grained Facial Expression Recognition. **Wenxuan Wang**, Yanwei Fu, Qiang Sun, Tao Chen, Chenjie Cao, Ziqi Zheng, Guoqiang Xu, Han Qiu, Yu-Gang Jiang, Xiangyang Xue. arXiv, 2019.
- A Fine-Grained Facial Expression Database for End-to-End Multi-Pose Facial Expression Recognition.
 Wenxuan Wang, Qiang Sun, Tao Chen, Chenjie Cao, Ziqi Zheng, Guoqiang Xu, Han Qiu, Yanwei Fu. arXiv, 2018.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Ping An Sep. 2018 – Jun. 2019

Algorithm Intern

- Facial expression recognition under few-shot setting project.
- Built a novel fine-grained facial expression dataset.
- Proposed an algorithm for recognizing subtle facial expressions in the insufficient training data condition.

Tencent Jun. 2020 – Jan. 2021

Algorithm Intern

- The adversarial examples and the robustness of the deep neural networks.
- Proposed a novel algorithm to realize black-box attack under data-free condition.

Recognition for to 1% of Ph.D students in GPA and academic achievements in Shanghai

• Introduced an algorithm to generate imperceptible and transferable attacks on face recognition system.

HONORS AND AWARDS

National Scholarship Recognition for to 1% of students in GPA at Northwestern Polytechnical University	2016-2017
First-class Scholarship for Excellent Master Students Recognition for to 10% of master students in academics at Fudan University	2017-2018
'Wei Rui' Scholarship Recognition for to 5% of Ph.D students in academics at Fudan University	2018-2019
First-class Scholarship for Excellent Ph.D Students Recognition for to 10% of Ph.D students in academics at Fudan University	2019-2020
First-class Scholarship for Excellent Ph.D Students Recognition for to 10% of Ph.D students in academics at Fudan University	2020-2021
Excellent Doctoral Dissertation of Fudan University Recognition for to 1% of Ph.D students in doctoral dissertation at Fudan University	2022
Outstanding Graduate of Shanghai	2022

EXTRA

2020 - 2022**Academic Activities** Reviewer: TPAMI, TNNLS, CVPR, ICCV, ECCV, AAAI, ACM MM Sep. 2018 - Feb. 2019 **Teaching Assistant** Information System Security Fudan University **Part-Time Teacher** Dec. 2018 – Jul. 2019 Teaching junior high school students Chinese, English and Physics

ZhangMen, Online